Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen Records 5148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 406 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Local 408 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Local 409 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Local 411 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Local 412 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Local 413 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Local 415 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Local 416 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Local 418 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Local 419 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Local 425 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Local 433 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Local 440 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Local 443 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Local 444 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Local 445 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Local 446 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Local 450 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Local 451 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Local 453 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Local 455 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Local 458 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Local 463 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Local 468 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Local 470 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Local 500 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Local 503 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Local 506 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Local 508 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Local 514 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Local 515 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Local 516 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Local 519 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Local 523 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Local 529 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Local 530 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Local 532 (Box 13, Folder 78)
- Local 538 (Box 13, Folder 79)
- Local 540 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- Local 543 (Box 13, Folder 81)
- Local 556 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Local 558 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Local 560 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Local 561 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Local 563 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- Local 566 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- Local 567 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- Local 568 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Local 570 (Box 13, Folder 90)
- Local 575 (Box 13, Folder 91)
- Local 577 (Box 13, Folder 92)
- Local 579 (Box 13, Folder 93)
- Local 580 (Box 13, Folder 94)
- Local 583 (Box 13, Folder 95)
- Local 584 (Box 13, Folder 96)
- Local 585 (Box 13, Folder 97)
- Local 591 (Box 13, Folder 98)
- Local 596 (Box 13, Folder 99)
- Local 597 (Box 13, Folder 100)
- Local 598 (Box 13, Folder 101)
- Local 599 (Box 13, Folder 102)
- Local 608 (Box 13, Folder 103)
- Local 609 (Box 13, Folder 104)
- Local 613 (Box 13, Folder 105)
- Local 616 (Box 13, Folder 106)
- Local 617 (Box 13, Folder 107)
- Local 619 (Box 13, Folder 108)
- Local 622 (Box 13, Folder 109)
- Local 625 (Box 13, Folder 110)
- Local 627 (Box 13, Folder 111)
- Local 629 (Box 13, Folder 112)
- Local 633 (Box 13, Folder 113)
- Local 634 (Box 13, Folder 114)
- Local 641 (Box 13, Folder 115)
- Local 642 (Box 13, Folder 116)
- Local 643 (Box 13, Folder 117)
- Local 645 (Box 13, Folder 118)
- Local 646 (Box 13, Folder 119)
- Local 647 (Box 13, Folder 120)
- Local 648 (Box 13, Folder 121)
- Local 649 (Box 13, Folder 122)
- Local 650 (Box 13, Folder 123)
- Local 651 (Box 13, Folder 124)
- Local 652 (Box 13, Folder 125)
- Local 654 (Box 13, Folder 126)
- Local 659 (Box 13, Folder 127)
- Local 661 (Box 13, Folder 128)
- Local 672 (Box 13, Folder 129)
- Local 677 (Box 13, Folder 130)
- Local 680 (Box 13, Folder 131)
- Local 682 (Box 13, Folder 132)
- Local 683 (Box 13, Folder 133)
- Local 684 (Box 13, Folder 134)
- Local 685 (Box 13, Folder 135)
- Local 688 (Box 13, Folder 136)
- Local 704 (Box 13, Folder 137)
- Local 709 (Box 13, Folder 138)
- Local 712 (Box 13, Folder 139)
- Local 715 (Box 13, Folder 140)
- Local 716 (Box 13, Folder 141)
- Local 719 (Box 13, Folder 142)
- Local 722 (Box 13, Folder 143)
- Local 723 (Box 13, Folder 144)
- Local 726 (Box 13, Folder 145)
- Local 728 (Box 13, Folder 146)
- Local 735 (Box 13, Folder 147)
- Local 737 (Box 13, Folder 148)
- Accident Ins. Dept. - Corres., 1917 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Advertising, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Re Amalgamation Report, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Authority from Insurance Commissioner (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Benefit Dept. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Conductors Examination (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Conductor & Brakemen's Assn., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Films Patent Rights - Photos, 1956-1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- ORC&B Convention, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Gen. Comm. Of Adjustment, 1892-1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Jurisprudence Committee Reports, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Grand Division Program, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- History (Box 14, Folder 13)
- History (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Merger (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Legislation, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Merger, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Merger (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Membership (Box 14, Folder 19)
- BRT - ORC&B - 2 Way Unification Document (Box 14, Folder 20)
- O. R. C. Days (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Membership Corres., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Misc. (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Railroad Conductor Mag. - Corres. (Box 14, Folder 24)
- The Railroad Conductor's Brotherhood Magazine, 1877 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- ORC Schedule, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Kate Shelley #1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Kate Shelley #2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Kate Shelley #3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Kate Shelley #4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Kate Shelley #5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Kate Shelley #6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Kate Shelley #7 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Kate Shelley #8 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Kate Shelley #9 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Kate Shelley #10 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Kate Shelley #11 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Kate Shelley #12 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Kate Shelley #13 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Invitation Lists - Kate Shelley Ceremony, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- The Boone News, Republican - Kate Shelley Ceremony, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  July 7, 1956
- Kate Shelley - ORC&B Photos & Negatives, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Kate Shelley - Speech at 75th Anniversary Ceremony, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Boone, Iowa
- Replies to Shelley RSVP's, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- ORC&B Railway Business Women's Assoc. Magazines re: Kate Shelley Ceremony, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Kate Shelley Memorial ORC&B, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  July 6, 1956
- The ORC&B Magazine re: Kate Shelley Ceremony, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  June 1956
- Arbitration - ORC & BRT vs. Eastern Railroads, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Book - October 28 - December 1, 1926
- 3-Way Unification - Declaration of Principles (Box 16, Folder 2)
- 3-Way Unification - Unification Agreement (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 3-Way Unification - Implementation Agreement (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 3-Way Unification - Constitution (Part I) (Box 16, Folder 5)
- 3-Way Unification - Constitution (Part II) (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Unification - ORC&B - BRT - SUNA - BL (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Conductor's, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Misc. (Box 16, Folder 9)
- NYS Full Crew Laws, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- NYS Full Crew Laws, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- NYS Full Crew Laws, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- National Railroad Adjustment Bd. - ORC&B and various railroad companies, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- United Trainmen's Assn. (Box 16, Folder 14)
- US RR Adjustment Board concerning ORC&B, 1955-1961 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- US RR Adjustment Board, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- US RR Adjustment Board, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- US RR Adjustment Board, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Presidents Emergency Board - Employees Rebuttal Exhibit No. 79, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Presidents Emergency Board - Employees Rebuttal Exhibit No. 82, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Arbitration Concerning ORC, 1910-1913 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- US RR Labor Board concerning ORC&B, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- C. & N. W. RR v. ORC&B, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- C. & N. W. RR v. ORC&B, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Alabama Great Southern (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe (Box 17, Folder 2)
- BRC - ORC, 1891 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Baltimore & Ohio (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Burlington, Cedar Rapids & Northern (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Cedar Rapids Telephone (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Chicago Great Western (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Chicago, Milwaukee & St. Paul (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Delaware, Lackawanna & Western (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Delaware, Lackawanna & Western (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Detroit & Toledo (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Eastern, Western & Southeastern (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Erie Railroad Co. (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Fidelity & Casualty Co. (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Indianapolis Union Railway Co. (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Kennecott Copper Corp. (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Mobile & Ohio RR (Box 17, Folder 18)
- National Agreement (Box 17, Folder 19)
- New York, Chicago & St. Louis (Box 17, Folder 20)
- New York, New Haven & Hartford (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh & Western (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Pullman Co. (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Rio Grande Southern RR (Box 17, Folder 24)
- River Terminal Railway (Box 17, Folder 25)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Co. (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Southern Pacific Co. (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Southern Pacific Co. (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Southern Railroad (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Spokane Int'l RR Co. (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Tennessee Coal & Iron RR Co. (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Texas & Pacific (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Tremont & Gulf (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Union Pacific Co. (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Union Pacific Co. (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Date File, 1901-1916 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  Book
- Date File, 1917-1918 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Date File, 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Date File, 1918-1924 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 18, Folder 3)
- File Claims Promptly, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- By-Laws, 1910-1954 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- ORC 42nd Grand Division, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- ORC Ritual, 1933-1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- ORC Burial Service (Box 18, Folder 8)
- ORC Song Sheet, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- The Railway Conductor, 1899-1913 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Accident Insurance Department (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Mutual Benefit Department Rate Book, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Group Policy Contracts, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Proposed Amendment to Accident Insurance Department Laws, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Health & Welfare Plan, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- ORC Directories, 1956-1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Rates of Pay, 1946-1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Creighton University Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Workshop, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Southern Pacific Lines 54th Annual Report, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Savannah: The Colossal City, William Scates, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- ORC 43rd Annual Division, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- ORC 45th Annual Division, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Boundsides, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- ORC Membership Candidate Questionnaire, 1890-1910 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- The Railroad Industry in the United States (Box 19, Folder 2)
- State & Federal Laws. California, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Rules for the Maintenance, Operating & Inspection of Air Brakes (Box 19, Folder 4)
  No Date
- Pocket Primer of Air-Brake Instruction, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Instructions Related to Superheater Locomotives, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Good Firing, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Diesel & Electric Locomotives, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Integral Train Systems, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Locomotive Valve Gears: Valve Setting, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Stokers, Superheaters, Headlights, Train Rules, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Locomotives & Their Operation, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Steam Locomotives & Boilers, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hand Firing & Locomotive Boiler Attachments, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Locomotive Brake Equipment: Air-Brake Vol. I, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Passenger & Freight-Car Brake Equipment: Air-Brake Vol. II, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 1, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Book - Pages 1-357 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 2, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Book - Pages 358-766 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 3, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Book - Pages 767-1157 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 4, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Book - Pages 1158-1534 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 5, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Book - Pages 1535-1915 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 6, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Book - Pages 1916-2328 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 7, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Book - Pages 2329-2701 Inc.
- 40th Grand Division Proceedings Volume 8, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Book - Pages 2702-2903 Inc.
- 42nd Grand Division Proceedings Volume 1, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- 42nd Grand Division Proceedings Volume 2, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- 42nd Grand Division Proceedings Volume 3, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- 42nd Grand Division Proceedings Volume 4, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 1, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 2, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 3, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 1, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 2, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Order of Railway Conductors & Brakemen Volume 3, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Scrapbook of Forms (Box 23, Folder 1)
- ORCB Charters "District Meeting, ORC 6-2-35" (Box 24)
  - ORC&B Charters (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 25)